♪ Listen close I have something to show you It is going to change everything I am freeing you from that heavy burden
The terminal was heavy and my soul was tired ♪
The terminal was heavy and my soul was tired
All those NPM packages that I once desired ♪
♪ The terminal was heavy and my soul was tired
All those NPM packages that I once desired
But now I declare my UI right from the source ♪
♪ All those NPM packages that I once desired
But now I declare my UI right from the source
And let Pathland take me on its beautiful course ♪
♪ But now I declare my UI right from the source
And let Pathland take me on its beautiful course
One DSL to rule them and to set us all free ♪
♪ And let Pathland take me on its beautiful course
One DSL to rule them and to set us all free
In the backend only logic is where I want to be ♪
♪ One DSL to rule them and to set us all free
In the backend only logic is where I want to be
No more frontend contracts that just rip me apart ♪
♪ In the backend only logic is where I want to be
No more frontend contracts that just rip me apart
This is pure declarative love right from the heart ♪
♪ No more frontend contracts that just rip me apart
This is pure declarative love right from the heart
Pathland is calling me to the light ♪
♪ This is pure declarative love right from the heart
Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night ♪
♪ Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains ♪
♪ We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins ♪
♪ No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong ♪
♪ Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song ♪
♪ Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song
Sixteen byte opcodes are all that we need ♪
♪ Singing our beautiful server side song
Sixteen byte opcodes are all that we need
Streaming pure deltas at a beautiful speed ♪
♪ Sixteen byte opcodes are all that we need
Streaming pure deltas at a beautiful speed
An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes in the dark ♪
♪ Streaming pure deltas at a beautiful speed
An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes in the dark
Leaving no trace of an unwanted mark ♪
♪ An unchanged screen transmits zero bytes in the dark
Leaving no trace of an unwanted mark
From Rust to Java it all looks the same ♪
♪ Leaving no trace of an unwanted mark
From Rust to Java it all looks the same
We finally ended that whole frontend game ♪
♪ From Rust to Java it all looks the same
We finally ended that whole frontend game
I can feel the relief in my very own bones ♪
♪ We finally ended that whole frontend game
I can feel the relief in my very own bones
Listening to these sweet binary tones ♪
♪ I can feel the relief in my very own bones
Listening to these sweet binary tones
Pathland is calling me to the light ♪
♪ Listening to these sweet binary tones
Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night ♪
♪ Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains ♪
♪ We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins ♪
♪ No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong ♪
♪ Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song ♪
♪ Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song
And as the tests turn a beautiful green ♪
♪
♪ Singing our beautiful server side song
And as the tests turn a beautiful green
We gaze upon the most flawless UI ever seen ♪
♪ And as the tests turn a beautiful green
We gaze upon the most flawless UI ever seen
Oh the future is bright and so crystal clear ♪
♪ We gaze upon the most flawless UI ever seen
Oh the future is bright and so crystal clear
We have absolutely nothing left to fear ♪
♪ Oh the future is bright and so crystal clear
We have absolutely nothing left to fear
Can you feel the power of this beautiful stream ♪
♪ We have absolutely nothing left to fear
Can you feel the power of this beautiful stream
It is everything we could possibly dream ♪
♪ Can you feel the power of this beautiful stream
It is everything we could possibly dream
Yes it is everything we could ever need ♪
♪ It is everything we could possibly dream
Yes it is everything we could ever need
Pathland is calling me to the light ♪
♪ Yes it is everything we could ever need
Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night ♪
♪ Pathland is calling me to the light
We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains ♪
♪ We are rendering natively into the night
No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins ♪
♪ No more complex frontend build toolchains
Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong ♪
♪ Just binary opcodes running through our veins
Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song ♪
♪ Yes Pathland is where we truly belong
Singing our beautiful server side song
Binary deltas are streaming through my mind ♪
♪ Singing our beautiful server side song
Binary deltas are streaming through my mind
Leaving all that unnecessary complexity far behind ♪
♪ Binary deltas are streaming through my mind
Leaving all that unnecessary complexity far behind
Just me and my pure server side views ♪
♪ Leaving all that unnecessary complexity far behind
Just me and my pure server side views
With nothing left to lose ♪
♪ Just me and my pure server side views
With nothing left to lose
(Ooh Pathland) (it is finally here) ♪
♪ With nothing left to lose
(Ooh Pathland) (it is finally here)
(Ooh Pathland) (our future is clear) ♪
♪ (Ooh Pathland) (it is finally here)